You now I think
maybe we're starting to
see just the little
beginnings of it you
in software encoding I
didn't see it within
Anthropic where you I
can look forward I
can kind look forward
to a where on
the more junior end
and then on the
more intermediate end we
actually need less and
not more people And
you we're thinking about
how to deal with
that within Anthropic in
a you in a
sensible way I
you one to five
years as of six
months ago I would
stick with that You
if you kind of
you connect this to
what I said before
which is you we
might have AI that's
better than humans at
everything in you maybe
one to two years
maybe a little longer
than that those don't
seem to line up
The reason is that
there's this lag and
there's this replacement thing
right I know that
the labour market is
adaptable right It's just
like you 80 of
people used to do
farming you got automated
and then they became
factory workers and then
knowledge workers So you
there is some level
of adaptability here as
well right We should
be economically sophisticated about
how the market works
But my worry is
as this exponential keeps
compounding and I don't
think it's going to
take that long again
somewhere between a year
and five years it
will overwhelm our ability
to adapt